ipipi.com 2006-12-30

# Send SMS Text Messages :: Privacy Policy

iPiPi is a service provided by Upside Wireless Inc. (Upside), located at Suite 503-535 Thurlow Street, Vancouver, BC, V6E 3L2, Canada. We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.html) for important information about safe surfing from the US Federal Trade Commission.**

**Coverage**

  * This policy covers how iPiPi treats personal information that our service collects and receives, including information related to your past use of iPiPi and your communications with iPiPi and Upside Wireless Inc. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Upside Wireless Inc. does not own or control, or to people that Upside does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

  * iPiPi collects personal information when you register with iPiPi, when you use our service, when you visit iPiPi pages or the pages of certain iPiPi partners, and when you enter promotions. IPiPi may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code and personal interests. Once you register with iPiPi and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * iPiPi collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.
  * iPiPi automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address, iPiPi cookie information, and the page you request.
  * iPiPi uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * **iPiPi does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you, nor contacts you enter in your address book,** with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with IPiPi under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help iPiPi communicate with you about offers from iPiPi and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of iPiPi's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if iPiPi is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, iPiPi will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * iPiPi displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.
    * iPiPi does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
    * iPiPi advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

**Cookies**

  * iPiPi may set and access iPiPi cookies on your computer.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * You can edit your iPiPi account information, including your preferences at any time.
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the iPiPi service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the iPiPi Newsletter, that are considered part of your iPiPi account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your iPiPi account by visiting the feedback form page and requesting that your account be deleted.  Please make sure that you include your iPiPi account name in this request.

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that protect personal information about you.
  * Your iPiPi Account Information is password-protected.
  * Your iPiPi password is encrypted.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * iPiPi may update this policy at any time. By continuing to use this service, you accept the new wording Privacy Policy.

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us here
